Register of the Polish Information Center (New York, N.Y.) Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILE, 1936-1952
  - World War, 1939-1945
    - Occupied countries (Folder 79: 8)
    - Polish contribution and war efforts (Folder 79: 9)
    - United States and Soviet Union wartime policies toward Poland, 1944
      - March (Folder 79: 10)
      - June (Folder 79: 11-13)
      - July (Box-folder 80: 1-7)
      - July (Box-folder 81: 1)
      - August (Folder 81: 2-7)
      - September (Folder 81: 8)
- PHONORECORDS, 1943 and undated (Box 82)
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Box 82 closed. Please contact the Hoover Institution for access.
  - General
    - Instrumental music by the Polish Army Band in Britain (Folder 82: 1)
      Side A: Goralski Marsz, Trojak (Polish Highland Airs and Dances) Side B: Tysiac Walecznych (Polish Independence Songs)
      Harmonia Records catalog number H-1026
      Access
      Use copy reference number: 48018_a_0012713
    - Instrumental and vocal music by Ignacy Podgorski and the Polish Dance Orchestra (Folder 82: 2)
      Side A: Pobor Na Dziewczyny Polka (The draft of the girls - Polka) Side B: Niema Jak Krakowiak (Krakowiak)
      Harmonia Records catalog number H-1040
      Use copy reference number: 48018_a_0012714
    - Vocal music (with piano accompaniment by J. Moliniak) issued by Radio Polskie in London
      - Boleslawski, Edward (Folder 82: 3)
        Skowroneczek Spiewa (The Lark)
        Use copy reference number: 48018_a_0012717
      - Nowakowski, Marian (Folder 82: 4)
        Choragiewka (St. Niewiadomski)
        Use copy reference number: 48018_a_0012718
  - "Poland Speaks from Britain"
    - Undated (Folder 82: 5-7)
      Part 1: March of 1st Regt. of Light Cavalry Part 2: March of 2nd Regt. of Uhlans Part 3: Cavalry March Part 4: The Highlanders March Part 5: March of Zouaves - 1863
      Use copy reference number: 48018_a_0012721
    - 1943 December 22 (Folder 82: 8-9)
      Set of Twelve Krakowiaks arr. Gerrard Williams Band of H.M. Scots Guards Conductor: Captain S. Rhodes
      Use copy reference number: 48018_a_0012726
- PHOTOGRAPHS, n.d. (Photo-file Photo file)
  - 12 prints of Polish refugee children in Great Britain and Africa during World War II (Photo-file mA)
  - 11 prints of scenes in Poland during World War II, and depicting the Polish troops training in Great Britain (Photo-file mB)